https://www.amadeus-equipment.co.uk/privacy-cookies-policies/

Products
BOXY - Modular Studios and Soundproof RoomsNext Generation M-Pod® - Soundproof Pods Ideal for Musicians‹Previous›NextAcoustic SolutionsView AllAcoustic DoorsAcoustic TreatmentSound Attenuated Acoustic RoomsPerformance EquipmentView AllAcoustic ShieldsConductors' PodiumsInstrument StorageMusic Stands and AccessoriesMusic Stand CartsMusic Stand LightsMusicians' Chairs and StoolsChair Storage CartsPortable Staging
Services
Acoustic ConsultancyViewSound management advice for an unlimited range of environmentsAuditorium DesignViewSpecialists in acoustic design, accessibility and comfortBespoke Instrument StorageViewStorage designed, planned and built to your specificationMusic Studio DesignViewBespoke studio design for the ultimate in acoustics and style
Story Page
Resources
Amadeus Knowledge Base
Glossary
Let’s Talk
Opus ¦ AMS ¦ M-Pod
Home » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Website Privacy Policy
Amadeus Acoustic Solutions & Amadeus Performance Equipment (Amadeus) are committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of anyone using our site.
Our website is built with WordPress.org and professionally hosted
to protect its functionality and security. WordPress core software (4.9.6 onwards) is GDPR compliant with functionality to export or remove a user’s personal data. Several WordPress plugins (“add-on” technology) are used to help ensure GDPR compliance throughout our website.
Any information submitted by our users will be considered strictly confidential. We will not use your personal details for any purpose other than to fulfill your specific request(s) via the form. Each of our forms offer an opt-in check box and a link to our Privacy Policy.
We will not disclose your personal data to any third party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the follow circumstances:
In the event that we sell any or all of our business to the buyer
Where we are legally required by law to disclose your personal information
To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud
In accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (May 2018), you have the right to access any information that we hold relating to you.
Contact Us form
Form entries are securely stored in our WordPress database and sent via email to Amadeus, where the data is used solely to fulfil your request or enquiry. A copy of your email will also be sent to your own email address. Your details will not be shared or used for marketing purposes unless we are given your explicit consent. Read more about WordPress.org & GDPR compliance.
Newsletter sign-up form
Form entries are securely stored by our provider, Mailchimp. Your details will be included on our newsletter subscription list. We will not share subsciber details unless we are given your explicit consent.
We will then send subscribers occasional emails regarding our services that we believe may be of interest to you. Subscribers to newsletters will be contacted solely using the Mailchimp interface and can unsubscribe at any time using that platform. Subscribers who are also a customer should unsubscribe via Mailchimp and contact Amadeus directly at info [@] amadeus-equipment.co.uk to discontinue all email communication. Read more about Mailchimp & GDPR compliance.
Third Party Links
Links to third parties are included on some pages of this website. These links are provided for additional information and to improve our visitor experience; however, the inclusion of a third party link does not mean that we endorse or approve that site’s privacy. Please review their own privacy policy.
Requesting Your Data
If you would like to request a copy of the personal data that we store about you, or have that data corrected or erased, please contact our DPO (below) in the first instance.
Data Protection Officer (DPO):
Anne Holliday, Managing Director
anne [@] amadeus-equipment.co.uk
Please also read our Cookie Policy.
Latest News
Curve Pusher Moves To HastingsCase Study – Curve Pusher Mastering Studios Introduction The founder of Curve Pusher, Vinyl, CD & Digital Mastering, Lawrie Dunster made a decis Read Article
Billy Cunningham Sevenoaks Drum SchoolUpdate Billy Cunningham Sevenoaks Drum School After some months of using his Amadeus Garden Studio; our client, Billy Cunningham decided to ring the c Read Article
School Dining Hall Acoustic ManagementDuring the summer of 2018 the schools Deputy Head made contact with Amadeus for advice on controlling a highly reverberative dining hall at St Mary Read Article
Follow Us
AMADEUS
ACOUSTIC SOLUTIONS
PERFORMANCE EQUIPMENT
Contact
Amadeus
Vantage Point, North Trade Road,
Battle,
East Sussex,
TN33 9LJ
+44 (0)1424 775867
+44 (0)1424 775866
info@amadeus-equipment.co.uk
Registered Office: Landgate Chamber, Rye, East Sussex, TN31 7LJ • Performance Equipment Registered No. 2958266 • Acoustic Solutions Registered No. 3800801Copyright © 2014 - 2020 Amadeus Equipment
Terms & Conditions
Terms of Website Use
Cookie Policy
Privacy Policy
Site & SEO Migrate Media
Please sign me up for the quarterly newsletter...
* indicates required
Email Address
*
First Name
Last Name
I give my consent to receive email newsletters & for my interactions with Amadeus' newsletters to be anonymously tracked via Mailchimp and Google Analytics. Privacy Policy
Please note, you can unsubscribe at any time.
Our website uses cookies. Follow the link to view our use of cookies or change your preferences. Allow Cookies
